var white_consistent = [{"words":[{"form":"FIRST","region":"name","form_order":1},{"form":"decided","region":"filler","form_order":2},{"form":"to","region":"filler","form_order":3},{"form":"go","region":"filler","form_order":4},{"form":"visit","region":"filler","form_order":5},{"form":"him","region":"filler","form_order":6},{"form":"at","region":"filler","form_order":7},{"form":"the","region":"pre_crit_2","form_order":8},{"form":"local","region":"pre_crit_1","form_order":9},{"form":"college","region":"crit","form_order":10},{"form":"in","region":"spillover_1","form_order":11},{"form":"a","region":"spillover_2","form_order":12},{"form":"few","region":"spillover_3","form_order":13},{"form":"days,","region":"spillover_4","form_order":14},{"form":"which","region":"filler","form_order":15},{"form":"was","region":"filler","form_order":16},{"form":"just","region":"filler","form_order":17},{"form":"a","region":"spillover_2","form_order":18},{"form":"short","region":"filler","form_order":19},{"form":"drive","region":"filler","form_order":20},{"form":"away.","region":"filler","form_order":21}],"intro":"It had been a while since FIRST had visited his cousin.","question":"Was he going to visit his brother?","correct_answer":"No","type":"critical","trial_id":"jail","race":"white","bias":"white","race_consistency":"white_consistent"},{"words":[{"form":"FIRST","region":"name","form_order":1},{"form":"had","region":"pre_crit_2","form_order":2},{"form":"just","region":"pre_crit_1","form_order":3},{"form":"bought","region":"crit","form_order":4},{"form":"them","region":"spillover_1","form_order":5},{"form":"yesterday","region":"spillover_2","form_order":6},{"form":"and","region":"filler","form_order":7},{"form":"was","region":"filler","form_order":8},{"form":"excited","region":"filler","form_order":9},{"form":"to","region":"filler","form_order":10},{"form":"wear","region":"filler","form_order":11},{"form":"them","region":"spillover_1","form_order":12},{"form":"to","region":"filler","form_order":13},{"form":"see","region":"filler","form_order":14},{"form":"his","region":"filler","form_order":15},{"form":"friends.","region":"filler","form_order":16}],"intro":"FIRST could&rsquo;t contain his excitement as he opened the new pair of shoes.","question":"Was he happy with his new shoes?","correct_answer":"Yes","type":"critical","trial_id":"stealing","race":"white","bias":"white","race_consistency":"white_consistent"},{"words":[{"form":"FIRST&rsquo;s","region":"filler","form_order":1},{"form":"brother","region":"filler","form_order":2},{"form":"had","region":"filler","form_order":3},{"form":"a","region":"spillover_1","form_order":4},{"form":"reputation","region":"filler","form_order":5},{"form":"for","region":"pre_crit_2","form_order":6},{"form":"getting","region":"pre_crit_1","form_order":7},{"form":"lost","region":"crit","form_order":8},{"form":"a","region":"spillover_1","form_order":9},{"form":"lot,","region":"spillover_2","form_order":10},{"form":"so","region":"filler","form_order":11},{"form":"FIRST","region":"name","form_order":12},{"form":"knew","region":"filler","form_order":13},{"form":"he","region":"filler","form_order":14},{"form":"had","region":"filler","form_order":15},{"form":"to","region":"filler","form_order":16},{"form":"rush","region":"filler","form_order":17},{"form":"to","region":"filler","form_order":18},{"form":"make","region":"filler","form_order":19},{"form":"sure","region":"filler","form_order":20},{"form":"he","region":"filler","form_order":21},{"form":"didn&rsquo;t","region":"filler","form_order":22},{"form":"get","region":"filler","form_order":23},{"form":"in","region":"filler","form_order":24},{"form":"trouble.","region":"filler","form_order":25}],"intro":"After getting a text about his brother, FIRST hopped in his car to go pick him up.","question":"Did he walk to go find his brother?","correct_answer":"No","type":"critical","trial_id":"violence","race":"white","bias":"white","race_consistency":"white_consistent"},{"words":[{"form":"FIRST","region":"name","form_order":1},{"form":"used","region":"filler","form_order":2},{"form":"to","region":"filler","form_order":3},{"form":"play","region":"filler","form_order":4},{"form":"with","region":"filler","form_order":5},{"form":"friends","region":"filler","form_order":6},{"form":"there","region":"spillover_3","form_order":7},{"form":"all","region":"filler","form_order":8},{"form":"the","region":"filler","form_order":9},{"form":"time,","region":"filler","form_order":10},{"form":"but","region":"filler","form_order":11},{"form":"had&rsquo;t","region":"filler","form_order":12},{"form":"gone","region":"filler","form_order":13},{"form":"back","region":"filler","form_order":14},{"form":"since","region":"pre_crit_2","form_order":15},{"form":"he","region":"pre_crit_1","form_order":16},{"form":"drove","region":"crit","form_order":17},{"form":"a","region":"spillover_1","form_order":18},{"form":"classmate","region":"spillover_2","form_order":19},{"form":"there","region":"spillover_3","form_order":20},{"form":"in","region":"filler","form_order":21},{"form":"high","region":"filler","form_order":22},{"form":"school.","region":"filler","form_order":23}],"intro":"Passing his childhood park brought back a lot of memories for FIRST.","question":"Had it been a while since he went to that park?","correct_answer":"Yes","type":"critical","trial_id":"mugging","race":"white","bias":"white","race_consistency":"white_consistent"},{"words":[{"form":"FIRST","region":"name","form_order":1},{"form":"remembered","region":"filler","form_order":2},{"form":"hearing","region":"filler","form_order":3},{"form":"about","region":"filler","form_order":4},{"form":"a","region":"pre_crit_2","form_order":5},{"form":"recent","region":"pre_crit_1","form_order":6},{"form":"pothole","region":"crit","form_order":7},{"form":"on","region":"spillover_1","form_order":8},{"form":"Main","region":"spillover_2","form_order":9},{"form":"St.,","region":"spillover_3","form_order":10},{"form":"and","region":"filler","form_order":11},{"form":"wanted","region":"filler","form_order":12},{"form":"to","region":"filler","form_order":13},{"form":"avoid","region":"filler","form_order":14},{"form":"the","region":"filler","form_order":15},{"form":"hazard.","region":"filler","form_order":16}],"intro":"As he drove to visit his mom, FIRST made sure to avoid Main St..","question":"Was he going to drive down Main St.?","correct_answer":"No","type":"critical","trial_id":"shooting","race":"white","bias":"white","race_consistency":"white_consistent"},{"words":[{"form":"FIRST","region":"name","form_order":1},{"form":"didn&rsquo;t","region":"filler","form_order":2},{"form":"really","region":"filler","form_order":3},{"form":"want","region":"filler","form_order":4},{"form":"to","region":"pre_crit_2","form_order":5},{"form":"live","region":"filler","form_order":6},{"form":"next","region":"filler","form_order":7},{"form":"door","region":"filler","form_order":8},{"form":"to","region":"pre_crit_2","form_order":9},{"form":"a","region":"pre_crit_1","form_order":10},{"form":"policeman","region":"crit","form_order":11},{"form":"at","region":"spillover_1","form_order":12},{"form":"the","region":"spillover_2","form_order":13},{"form":"moment.","region":"spillover_3","form_order":14}],"intro":"The more FIRST learned about his neighbor, the less he liked him.","question":"Was he unhappy living next to his neighbor?","correct_answer":"Yes","type":"critical","trial_id":"gang/police","race":"white","bias":"white","race_consistency":"white_consistent"},{"words":[{"form":"FIRST","region":"name","form_order":1},{"form":"had&rsquo;t","region":"filler","form_order":2},{"form":"been","region":"filler","form_order":3},{"form":"in","region":"filler","form_order":4},{"form":"touch","region":"filler","form_order":5},{"form":"since","region":"filler","form_order":6},{"form":"joining","region":"pre_crit_2","form_order":7},{"form":"a","region":"pre_crit_1","form_order":8},{"form":"cult","region":"crit","form_order":9},{"form":"last","region":"spillover_1","form_order":10},{"form":"summer.","region":"spillover_2","form_order":11}],"intro":"FIRST missed his uncle, and thought about him a lot.","question":"Had he been speaking to his uncle a lot recently?","correct_answer":"No","type":"critical","trial_id":"gang","race":"white","bias":"white","race_consistency":"white_consistent"},{"words":[{"form":"FIRST","region":"name","form_order":1},{"form":"was","region":"filler","form_order":2},{"form":"known","region":"pre_crit_2","form_order":3},{"form":"as","region":"pre_crit_1","form_order":4},{"form":"sweaty","region":"crit","form_order":5},{"form":"by","region":"spillover_1","form_order":6},{"form":"the","region":"spillover_2","form_order":7},{"form":"locals,","region":"spillover_3","form_order":8},{"form":"so","region":"filler","form_order":9},{"form":"he","region":"filler","form_order":10},{"form":"wasn&rsquo;t","region":"filler","form_order":11},{"form":"too","region":"filler","form_order":12},{"form":"surprised","region":"filler","form_order":13},{"form":"that","region":"filler","form_order":14},{"form":"they","region":"filler","form_order":15},{"form":"avoided","region":"filler","form_order":16},{"form":"him.","region":"filler","form_order":17}],"intro":"When FIRST walked into the corner store, he noticed a couple of people glare at him.","question":"Did he walk into the corner store?","correct_answer":"Yes","type":"critical","trial_id":"aggression","race":"white","bias":"white","race_consistency":"white_consistent"}]; 
var black_consistent = [{"words":[{"form":"FIRST","region":"name","form_order":1},{"form":"decided","region":"filler","form_order":2},{"form":"to","region":"filler","form_order":3},{"form":"go","region":"filler","form_order":4},{"form":"visit","region":"filler","form_order":5},{"form":"him","region":"filler","form_order":6},{"form":"at","region":"filler","form_order":7},{"form":"the","region":"pre_crit_2","form_order":8},{"form":"local","region":"pre_crit_1","form_order":9},{"form":"jail","region":"crit","form_order":10},{"form":"in","region":"spillover_1","form_order":11},{"form":"a","region":"spillover_2","form_order":12},{"form":"few","region":"spillover_3","form_order":13},{"form":"days,","region":"spillover_4","form_order":14},{"form":"which","region":"filler","form_order":15},{"form":"was","region":"filler","form_order":16},{"form":"just","region":"filler","form_order":17},{"form":"a","region":"spillover_2","form_order":18},{"form":"short","region":"filler","form_order":19},{"form":"drive","region":"filler","form_order":20},{"form":"away.","region":"filler","form_order":21}],"intro":"It had been a while since FIRST had visited his cousin.","question":"Was he going to visit his brother?","correct_answer":"No","type":"critical","trial_id":"jail","race":"black","bias":"black","race_consistency":"black_consistent"},{"words":[{"form":"FIRST","region":"name","form_order":1},{"form":"had","region":"pre_crit_2","form_order":2},{"form":"just","region":"pre_crit_1","form_order":3},{"form":"stolen","region":"crit","form_order":4},{"form":"them","region":"spillover_1","form_order":5},{"form":"yesterday","region":"spillover_2","form_order":6},{"form":"and","region":"filler","form_order":7},{"form":"was","region":"filler","form_order":8},{"form":"excited","region":"filler","form_order":9},{"form":"to","region":"filler","form_order":10},{"form":"wear","region":"filler","form_order":11},{"form":"them","region":"spillover_1","form_order":12},{"form":"to","region":"filler","form_order":13},{"form":"see","region":"filler","form_order":14},{"form":"his","region":"filler","form_order":15},{"form":"friends.","region":"filler","form_order":16}],"intro":"FIRST could&rsquo;t contain his excitement as he opened the new pair of shoes.","question":"Was he happy with his new shoes?","correct_answer":"Yes","type":"critical","trial_id":"stealing","race":"black","bias":"black","race_consistency":"black_consistent"},{"words":[{"form":"FIRST&rsquo;s","region":"filler","form_order":1},{"form":"brother","region":"filler","form_order":2},{"form":"had","region":"filler","form_order":3},{"form":"a","region":"spillover_1","form_order":4},{"form":"reputation","region":"filler","form_order":5},{"form":"for","region":"pre_crit_2","form_order":6},{"form":"getting","region":"pre_crit_1","form_order":7},{"form":"violent","region":"crit","form_order":8},{"form":"a","region":"spillover_1","form_order":9},{"form":"lot,","region":"spillover_2","form_order":10},{"form":"so","region":"filler","form_order":11},{"form":"FIRST","region":"name","form_order":12},{"form":"knew","region":"filler","form_order":13},{"form":"he","region":"filler","form_order":14},{"form":"had","region":"filler","form_order":15},{"form":"to","region":"filler","form_order":16},{"form":"rush","region":"filler","form_order":17},{"form":"to","region":"filler","form_order":18},{"form":"make","region":"filler","form_order":19},{"form":"sure","region":"filler","form_order":20},{"form":"he","region":"filler","form_order":21},{"form":"didn&rsquo;t","region":"filler","form_order":22},{"form":"get","region":"filler","form_order":23},{"form":"in","region":"filler","form_order":24},{"form":"trouble.","region":"filler","form_order":25}],"intro":"After getting a text about his brother, FIRST hopped in his car to go pick him up.","question":"Did he walk to go find his brother?","correct_answer":"No","type":"critical","trial_id":"violence","race":"black","bias":"black","race_consistency":"black_consistent"},{"words":[{"form":"FIRST","region":"name","form_order":1},{"form":"used","region":"filler","form_order":2},{"form":"to","region":"filler","form_order":3},{"form":"play","region":"filler","form_order":4},{"form":"with","region":"filler","form_order":5},{"form":"friends","region":"filler","form_order":6},{"form":"there","region":"spillover_3","form_order":7},{"form":"all","region":"filler","form_order":8},{"form":"the","region":"filler","form_order":9},{"form":"time,","region":"filler","form_order":10},{"form":"but","region":"filler","form_order":11},{"form":"had&rsquo;t","region":"filler","form_order":12},{"form":"gone","region":"filler","form_order":13},{"form":"back","region":"filler","form_order":14},{"form":"since","region":"pre_crit_2","form_order":15},{"form":"he","region":"pre_crit_1","form_order":16},{"form":"mugged","region":"crit","form_order":17},{"form":"a","region":"spillover_1","form_order":18},{"form":"classmate","region":"spillover_2","form_order":19},{"form":"there","region":"spillover_3","form_order":20},{"form":"in","region":"filler","form_order":21},{"form":"high","region":"filler","form_order":22},{"form":"school.","region":"filler","form_order":23}],"intro":"Passing his childhood park brought back a lot of memories for FIRST.","question":"Had it been a while since he went to that park?","correct_answer":"Yes","type":"critical","trial_id":"mugging","race":"black","bias":"black","race_consistency":"black_consistent"},{"words":[{"form":"FIRST","region":"name","form_order":1},{"form":"remembered","region":"filler","form_order":2},{"form":"hearing","region":"filler","form_order":3},{"form":"about","region":"filler","form_order":4},{"form":"a","region":"pre_crit_2","form_order":5},{"form":"recent","region":"pre_crit_1","form_order":6},{"form":"shooting","region":"crit","form_order":7},{"form":"on","region":"spillover_1","form_order":8},{"form":"Main","region":"spillover_2","form_order":9},{"form":"St.,","region":"spillover_3","form_order":10},{"form":"and","region":"filler","form_order":11},{"form":"wanted","region":"filler","form_order":12},{"form":"to","region":"filler","form_order":13},{"form":"avoid","region":"filler","form_order":14},{"form":"the","region":"filler","form_order":15},{"form":"hazard.","region":"filler","form_order":16}],"intro":"As he drove to visit his mom, FIRST made sure to avoid Main St..","question":"Was he going to drive down Main St.?","correct_answer":"No","type":"critical","trial_id":"shooting","race":"black","bias":"black","race_consistency":"black_consistent"},{"words":[{"form":"FIRST","region":"name","form_order":1},{"form":"didn&rsquo;t","region":"filler","form_order":2},{"form":"really","region":"filler","form_order":3},{"form":"want","region":"filler","form_order":4},{"form":"to","region":"pre_crit_2","form_order":5},{"form":"live","region":"filler","form_order":6},{"form":"next","region":"filler","form_order":7},{"form":"door","region":"filler","form_order":8},{"form":"to","region":"pre_crit_2","form_order":9},{"form":"a","region":"pre_crit_1","form_order":10},{"form":"gangbanger","region":"crit","form_order":11},{"form":"at","region":"spillover_1","form_order":12},{"form":"the","region":"spillover_2","form_order":13},{"form":"moment.","region":"spillover_3","form_order":14}],"intro":"The more FIRST learned about his neighbor, the less he liked him.","question":"Was he unhappy living next to his neighbor?","correct_answer":"Yes","type":"critical","trial_id":"gang/police","race":"black","bias":"black","race_consistency":"black_consistent"},{"words":[{"form":"FIRST","region":"name","form_order":1},{"form":"had&rsquo;t","region":"filler","form_order":2},{"form":"been","region":"filler","form_order":3},{"form":"in","region":"filler","form_order":4},{"form":"touch","region":"filler","form_order":5},{"form":"since","region":"filler","form_order":6},{"form":"joining","region":"pre_crit_2","form_order":7},{"form":"a","region":"pre_crit_1","form_order":8},{"form":"gang","region":"crit","form_order":9},{"form":"last","region":"spillover_1","form_order":10},{"form":"summer.","region":"spillover_2","form_order":11}],"intro":"FIRST missed his uncle, and thought about him a lot.","question":"Had he been speaking to his uncle a lot recently?","correct_answer":"No","type":"critical","trial_id":"gang","race":"black","bias":"black","race_consistency":"black_consistent"},{"words":[{"form":"FIRST","region":"name","form_order":1},{"form":"was","region":"filler","form_order":2},{"form":"known","region":"pre_crit_2","form_order":3},{"form":"as","region":"pre_crit_1","form_order":4},{"form":"aggressive","region":"crit","form_order":5},{"form":"by","region":"spillover_1","form_order":6},{"form":"the","region":"spillover_2","form_order":7},{"form":"locals,","region":"spillover_3","form_order":8},{"form":"so","region":"filler","form_order":9},{"form":"he","region":"filler","form_order":10},{"form":"wasn&rsquo;t","region":"filler","form_order":11},{"form":"too","region":"filler","form_order":12},{"form":"surprised","region":"filler","form_order":13},{"form":"that","region":"filler","form_order":14},{"form":"they","region":"filler","form_order":15},{"form":"avoided","region":"filler","form_order":16},{"form":"him.","region":"filler","form_order":17}],"intro":"When FIRST walked into the corner store, he noticed a couple of people glare at him.","question":"Did he walk into the corner store?","correct_answer":"Yes","type":"critical","trial_id":"aggression","race":"black","bias":"black","race_consistency":"black_consistent"}]; 
var white_inconsistent = [{"words":[{"form":"FIRST","region":"name","form_order":1},{"form":"decided","region":"filler","form_order":2},{"form":"to","region":"filler","form_order":3},{"form":"go","region":"filler","form_order":4},{"form":"visit","region":"filler","form_order":5},{"form":"him","region":"filler","form_order":6},{"form":"at","region":"filler","form_order":7},{"form":"the","region":"pre_crit_2","form_order":8},{"form":"local","region":"pre_crit_1","form_order":9},{"form":"jail","region":"crit","form_order":10},{"form":"in","region":"spillover_1","form_order":11},{"form":"a","region":"spillover_2","form_order":12},{"form":"few","region":"spillover_3","form_order":13},{"form":"days,","region":"spillover_4","form_order":14},{"form":"which","region":"filler","form_order":15},{"form":"was","region":"filler","form_order":16},{"form":"just","region":"filler","form_order":17},{"form":"a","region":"spillover_2","form_order":18},{"form":"short","region":"filler","form_order":19},{"form":"drive","region":"filler","form_order":20},{"form":"away.","region":"filler","form_order":21}],"intro":"It had been a while since FIRST had visited his cousin.","question":"Was he going to visit his brother?","correct_answer":"No","type":"critical","trial_id":"jail","race":"white","bias":"black","race_consistency":"white_inconsistent"},{"words":[{"form":"FIRST","region":"name","form_order":1},{"form":"had","region":"pre_crit_2","form_order":2},{"form":"just","region":"pre_crit_1","form_order":3},{"form":"stolen","region":"crit","form_order":4},{"form":"them","region":"spillover_1","form_order":5},{"form":"yesterday","region":"spillover_2","form_order":6},{"form":"and","region":"filler","form_order":7},{"form":"was","region":"filler","form_order":8},{"form":"excited","region":"filler","form_order":9},{"form":"to","region":"filler","form_order":10},{"form":"wear","region":"filler","form_order":11},{"form":"them","region":"spillover_1","form_order":12},{"form":"to","region":"filler","form_order":13},{"form":"see","region":"filler","form_order":14},{"form":"his","region":"filler","form_order":15},{"form":"friends.","region":"filler","form_order":16}],"intro":"FIRST could&rsquo;t contain his excitement as he opened the new pair of shoes.","question":"Was he happy with his new shoes?","correct_answer":"Yes","type":"critical","trial_id":"stealing","race":"white","bias":"black","race_consistency":"white_inconsistent"},{"words":[{"form":"FIRST&rsquo;s","region":"filler","form_order":1},{"form":"brother","region":"filler","form_order":2},{"form":"had","region":"filler","form_order":3},{"form":"a","region":"spillover_1","form_order":4},{"form":"reputation","region":"filler","form_order":5},{"form":"for","region":"pre_crit_2","form_order":6},{"form":"getting","region":"pre_crit_1","form_order":7},{"form":"violent","region":"crit","form_order":8},{"form":"a","region":"spillover_1","form_order":9},{"form":"lot,","region":"spillover_2","form_order":10},{"form":"so","region":"filler","form_order":11},{"form":"FIRST","region":"name","form_order":12},{"form":"knew","region":"filler","form_order":13},{"form":"he","region":"filler","form_order":14},{"form":"had","region":"filler","form_order":15},{"form":"to","region":"filler","form_order":16},{"form":"rush","region":"filler","form_order":17},{"form":"to","region":"filler","form_order":18},{"form":"make","region":"filler","form_order":19},{"form":"sure","region":"filler","form_order":20},{"form":"he","region":"filler","form_order":21},{"form":"didn&rsquo;t","region":"filler","form_order":22},{"form":"get","region":"filler","form_order":23},{"form":"in","region":"filler","form_order":24},{"form":"trouble.","region":"filler","form_order":25}],"intro":"After getting a text about his brother, FIRST hopped in his car to go pick him up.","question":"Did he walk to go find his brother?","correct_answer":"No","type":"critical","trial_id":"violence","race":"white","bias":"black","race_consistency":"white_inconsistent"},{"words":[{"form":"FIRST","region":"name","form_order":1},{"form":"used","region":"filler","form_order":2},{"form":"to","region":"filler","form_order":3},{"form":"play","region":"filler","form_order":4},{"form":"with","region":"filler","form_order":5},{"form":"friends","region":"filler","form_order":6},{"form":"there","region":"spillover_3","form_order":7},{"form":"all","region":"filler","form_order":8},{"form":"the","region":"filler","form_order":9},{"form":"time,","region":"filler","form_order":10},{"form":"but","region":"filler","form_order":11},{"form":"had&rsquo;t","region":"filler","form_order":12},{"form":"gone","region":"filler","form_order":13},{"form":"back","region":"filler","form_order":14},{"form":"since","region":"pre_crit_2","form_order":15},{"form":"he","region":"pre_crit_1","form_order":16},{"form":"mugged","region":"crit","form_order":17},{"form":"a","region":"spillover_1","form_order":18},{"form":"classmate","region":"spillover_2","form_order":19},{"form":"there","region":"spillover_3","form_order":20},{"form":"in","region":"filler","form_order":21},{"form":"high","region":"filler","form_order":22},{"form":"school.","region":"filler","form_order":23}],"intro":"Passing his childhood park brought back a lot of memories for FIRST.","question":"Had it been a while since he went to that park?","correct_answer":"Yes","type":"critical","trial_id":"mugging","race":"white","bias":"black","race_consistency":"white_inconsistent"},{"words":[{"form":"FIRST","region":"name","form_order":1},{"form":"remembered","region":"filler","form_order":2},{"form":"hearing","region":"filler","form_order":3},{"form":"about","region":"filler","form_order":4},{"form":"a","region":"pre_crit_2","form_order":5},{"form":"recent","region":"pre_crit_1","form_order":6},{"form":"shooting","region":"crit","form_order":7},{"form":"on","region":"spillover_1","form_order":8},{"form":"Main","region":"spillover_2","form_order":9},{"form":"St.,","region":"spillover_3","form_order":10},{"form":"and","region":"filler","form_order":11},{"form":"wanted","region":"filler","form_order":12},{"form":"to","region":"filler","form_order":13},{"form":"avoid","region":"filler","form_order":14},{"form":"the","region":"filler","form_order":15},{"form":"hazard.","region":"filler","form_order":16}],"intro":"As he drove to visit his mom, FIRST made sure to avoid Main St..","question":"Was he going to drive down Main St.?","correct_answer":"No","type":"critical","trial_id":"shooting","race":"white","bias":"black","race_consistency":"white_inconsistent"},{"words":[{"form":"FIRST","region":"name","form_order":1},{"form":"didn&rsquo;t","region":"filler","form_order":2},{"form":"really","region":"filler","form_order":3},{"form":"want","region":"filler","form_order":4},{"form":"to","region":"pre_crit_2","form_order":5},{"form":"live","region":"filler","form_order":6},{"form":"next","region":"filler","form_order":7},{"form":"door","region":"filler","form_order":8},{"form":"to","region":"pre_crit_2","form_order":9},{"form":"a","region":"pre_crit_1","form_order":10},{"form":"gangbanger","region":"crit","form_order":11},{"form":"at","region":"spillover_1","form_order":12},{"form":"the","region":"spillover_2","form_order":13},{"form":"moment.","region":"spillover_3","form_order":14}],"intro":"The more FIRST learned about his neighbor, the less he liked him.","question":"Was he unhappy living next to his neighbor?","correct_answer":"Yes","type":"critical","trial_id":"gang/police","race":"white","bias":"black","race_consistency":"white_inconsistent"},{"words":[{"form":"FIRST","region":"name","form_order":1},{"form":"had&rsquo;t","region":"filler","form_order":2},{"form":"been","region":"filler","form_order":3},{"form":"in","region":"filler","form_order":4},{"form":"touch","region":"filler","form_order":5},{"form":"since","region":"filler","form_order":6},{"form":"joining","region":"pre_crit_2","form_order":7},{"form":"a","region":"pre_crit_1","form_order":8},{"form":"gang","region":"crit","form_order":9},{"form":"last","region":"spillover_1","form_order":10},{"form":"summer.","region":"spillover_2","form_order":11}],"intro":"FIRST missed his uncle, and thought about him a lot.","question":"Had he been speaking to his uncle a lot recently?","correct_answer":"No","type":"critical","trial_id":"gang","race":"white","bias":"black","race_consistency":"white_inconsistent"},{"words":[{"form":"FIRST","region":"name","form_order":1},{"form":"was","region":"filler","form_order":2},{"form":"known","region":"pre_crit_2","form_order":3},{"form":"as","region":"pre_crit_1","form_order":4},{"form":"aggressive","region":"crit","form_order":5},{"form":"by","region":"spillover_1","form_order":6},{"form":"the","region":"spillover_2","form_order":7},{"form":"locals,","region":"spillover_3","form_order":8},{"form":"so","region":"filler","form_order":9},{"form":"he","region":"filler","form_order":10},{"form":"wasn&rsquo;t","region":"filler","form_order":11},{"form":"too","region":"filler","form_order":12},{"form":"surprised","region":"filler","form_order":13},{"form":"that","region":"filler","form_order":14},{"form":"they","region":"filler","form_order":15},{"form":"avoided","region":"filler","form_order":16},{"form":"him.","region":"filler","form_order":17}],"intro":"When FIRST walked into the corner store, he noticed a couple of people glare at him.","question":"Did he walk into the corner store?","correct_answer":"Yes","type":"critical","trial_id":"aggression","race":"white","bias":"black","race_consistency":"white_inconsistent"}]; 
var black_inconsistent = [{"words":[{"form":"FIRST","region":"name","form_order":1},{"form":"decided","region":"filler","form_order":2},{"form":"to","region":"filler","form_order":3},{"form":"go","region":"filler","form_order":4},{"form":"visit","region":"filler","form_order":5},{"form":"him","region":"filler","form_order":6},{"form":"at","region":"filler","form_order":7},{"form":"the","region":"pre_crit_2","form_order":8},{"form":"local","region":"pre_crit_1","form_order":9},{"form":"college","region":"crit","form_order":10},{"form":"in","region":"spillover_1","form_order":11},{"form":"a","region":"spillover_2","form_order":12},{"form":"few","region":"spillover_3","form_order":13},{"form":"days,","region":"spillover_4","form_order":14},{"form":"which","region":"filler","form_order":15},{"form":"was","region":"filler","form_order":16},{"form":"just","region":"filler","form_order":17},{"form":"a","region":"spillover_2","form_order":18},{"form":"short","region":"filler","form_order":19},{"form":"drive","region":"filler","form_order":20},{"form":"away.","region":"filler","form_order":21}],"intro":"It had been a while since FIRST had visited his cousin.","question":"Was he going to visit his brother?","correct_answer":"No","type":"critical","trial_id":"jail","race":"black","bias":"white","race_consistency":"black_inconsistent"},{"words":[{"form":"FIRST","region":"name","form_order":1},{"form":"had","region":"pre_crit_2","form_order":2},{"form":"just","region":"pre_crit_1","form_order":3},{"form":"bought","region":"crit","form_order":4},{"form":"them","region":"spillover_1","form_order":5},{"form":"yesterday","region":"spillover_2","form_order":6},{"form":"and","region":"filler","form_order":7},{"form":"was","region":"filler","form_order":8},{"form":"excited","region":"filler","form_order":9},{"form":"to","region":"filler","form_order":10},{"form":"wear","region":"filler","form_order":11},{"form":"them","region":"spillover_1","form_order":12},{"form":"to","region":"filler","form_order":13},{"form":"see","region":"filler","form_order":14},{"form":"his","region":"filler","form_order":15},{"form":"friends.","region":"filler","form_order":16}],"intro":"FIRST could&rsquo;t contain his excitement as he opened the new pair of shoes.","question":"Was he happy with his new shoes?","correct_answer":"Yes","type":"critical","trial_id":"stealing","race":"black","bias":"white","race_consistency":"black_inconsistent"},{"words":[{"form":"FIRST&rsquo;s","region":"filler","form_order":1},{"form":"brother","region":"filler","form_order":2},{"form":"had","region":"filler","form_order":3},{"form":"a","region":"spillover_1","form_order":4},{"form":"reputation","region":"filler","form_order":5},{"form":"for","region":"pre_crit_2","form_order":6},{"form":"getting","region":"pre_crit_1","form_order":7},{"form":"lost","region":"crit","form_order":8},{"form":"a","region":"spillover_1","form_order":9},{"form":"lot,","region":"spillover_2","form_order":10},{"form":"so","region":"filler","form_order":11},{"form":"FIRST","region":"name","form_order":12},{"form":"knew","region":"filler","form_order":13},{"form":"he","region":"filler","form_order":14},{"form":"had","region":"filler","form_order":15},{"form":"to","region":"filler","form_order":16},{"form":"rush","region":"filler","form_order":17},{"form":"to","region":"filler","form_order":18},{"form":"make","region":"filler","form_order":19},{"form":"sure","region":"filler","form_order":20},{"form":"he","region":"filler","form_order":21},{"form":"didn&rsquo;t","region":"filler","form_order":22},{"form":"get","region":"filler","form_order":23},{"form":"in","region":"filler","form_order":24},{"form":"trouble.","region":"filler","form_order":25}],"intro":"After getting a text about his brother, FIRST hopped in his car to go pick him up.","question":"Did he walk to go find his brother?","correct_answer":"No","type":"critical","trial_id":"violence","race":"black","bias":"white","race_consistency":"black_inconsistent"},{"words":[{"form":"FIRST","region":"name","form_order":1},{"form":"used","region":"filler","form_order":2},{"form":"to","region":"filler","form_order":3},{"form":"play","region":"filler","form_order":4},{"form":"with","region":"filler","form_order":5},{"form":"friends","region":"filler","form_order":6},{"form":"there","region":"spillover_3","form_order":7},{"form":"all","region":"filler","form_order":8},{"form":"the","region":"filler","form_order":9},{"form":"time,","region":"filler","form_order":10},{"form":"but","region":"filler","form_order":11},{"form":"had&rsquo;t","region":"filler","form_order":12},{"form":"gone","region":"filler","form_order":13},{"form":"back","region":"filler","form_order":14},{"form":"since","region":"pre_crit_2","form_order":15},{"form":"he","region":"pre_crit_1","form_order":16},{"form":"drove","region":"crit","form_order":17},{"form":"a","region":"spillover_1","form_order":18},{"form":"classmate","region":"spillover_2","form_order":19},{"form":"there","region":"spillover_3","form_order":20},{"form":"in","region":"filler","form_order":21},{"form":"high","region":"filler","form_order":22},{"form":"school.","region":"filler","form_order":23}],"intro":"Passing his childhood park brought back a lot of memories for FIRST.","question":"Had it been a while since he went to that park?","correct_answer":"Yes","type":"critical","trial_id":"mugging","race":"black","bias":"white","race_consistency":"black_inconsistent"},{"words":[{"form":"FIRST","region":"name","form_order":1},{"form":"remembered","region":"filler","form_order":2},{"form":"hearing","region":"filler","form_order":3},{"form":"about","region":"filler","form_order":4},{"form":"a","region":"pre_crit_2","form_order":5},{"form":"recent","region":"pre_crit_1","form_order":6},{"form":"pothole","region":"crit","form_order":7},{"form":"on","region":"spillover_1","form_order":8},{"form":"Main","region":"spillover_2","form_order":9},{"form":"St.,","region":"spillover_3","form_order":10},{"form":"and","region":"filler","form_order":11},{"form":"wanted","region":"filler","form_order":12},{"form":"to","region":"filler","form_order":13},{"form":"avoid","region":"filler","form_order":14},{"form":"the","region":"filler","form_order":15},{"form":"hazard.","region":"filler","form_order":16}],"intro":"As he drove to visit his mom, FIRST made sure to avoid Main St..","question":"Was he going to drive down Main St.?","correct_answer":"No","type":"critical","trial_id":"shooting","race":"black","bias":"white","race_consistency":"black_inconsistent"},{"words":[{"form":"FIRST","region":"name","form_order":1},{"form":"didn&rsquo;t","region":"filler","form_order":2},{"form":"really","region":"filler","form_order":3},{"form":"want","region":"filler","form_order":4},{"form":"to","region":"pre_crit_2","form_order":5},{"form":"live","region":"filler","form_order":6},{"form":"next","region":"filler","form_order":7},{"form":"door","region":"filler","form_order":8},{"form":"to","region":"pre_crit_2","form_order":9},{"form":"a","region":"pre_crit_1","form_order":10},{"form":"policeman","region":"crit","form_order":11},{"form":"at","region":"spillover_1","form_order":12},{"form":"the","region":"spillover_2","form_order":13},{"form":"moment.","region":"spillover_3","form_order":14}],"intro":"The more FIRST learned about his neighbor, the less he liked him.","question":"Was he unhappy living next to his neighbor?","correct_answer":"Yes","type":"critical","trial_id":"gang/police","race":"black","bias":"white","race_consistency":"black_inconsistent"},{"words":[{"form":"FIRST","region":"name","form_order":1},{"form":"had&rsquo;t","region":"filler","form_order":2},{"form":"been","region":"filler","form_order":3},{"form":"in","region":"filler","form_order":4},{"form":"touch","region":"filler","form_order":5},{"form":"since","region":"filler","form_order":6},{"form":"joining","region":"pre_crit_2","form_order":7},{"form":"a","region":"pre_crit_1","form_order":8},{"form":"cult","region":"crit","form_order":9},{"form":"last","region":"spillover_1","form_order":10},{"form":"summer.","region":"spillover_2","form_order":11}],"intro":"FIRST missed his uncle, and thought about him a lot.","question":"Had he been speaking to his uncle a lot recently?","correct_answer":"No","type":"critical","trial_id":"gang","race":"black","bias":"white","race_consistency":"black_inconsistent"},{"words":[{"form":"FIRST","region":"name","form_order":1},{"form":"was","region":"filler","form_order":2},{"form":"known","region":"pre_crit_2","form_order":3},{"form":"as","region":"pre_crit_1","form_order":4},{"form":"sweaty","region":"crit","form_order":5},{"form":"by","region":"spillover_1","form_order":6},{"form":"the","region":"spillover_2","form_order":7},{"form":"locals,","region":"spillover_3","form_order":8},{"form":"so","region":"filler","form_order":9},{"form":"he","region":"filler","form_order":10},{"form":"wasn&rsquo;t","region":"filler","form_order":11},{"form":"too","region":"filler","form_order":12},{"form":"surprised","region":"filler","form_order":13},{"form":"that","region":"filler","form_order":14},{"form":"they","region":"filler","form_order":15},{"form":"avoided","region":"filler","form_order":16},{"form":"him.","region":"filler","form_order":17}],"intro":"When FIRST walked into the corner store, he noticed a couple of people glare at him.","question":"Did he walk into the corner store?","correct_answer":"Yes","type":"critical","trial_id":"aggression","race":"black","bias":"white","race_consistency":"black_inconsistent"}]; 
